

// ABOUT ME

I am an Electronic Engineer by profession.

I like to always learn the new and share it with my work group, I currently have knowledge and experience developing in JavaScript, Front-End (ReactJS, React-native), Back-End (NodeJs, Express-JS) and Testing with JEST, with full interest and willingness to work as front end react developer.

In my projects, I love use **GIT** for version control



LinkedIn

http://linkedin.com/in/jeffrey-torresbello-1ab800171

Github: jetobe95

HakerRank: @alto_951



SKILLS

LANGUAGES

Strong Javascript • HTML • CSS Familiar

Java • PHP •Dart •

Python • SQL

OTHER

Mysql • MongoDB • CSS Shell • Git



HOBBIES



Learn & practice new dev tools on YouTube



Play guitar and gym

JEFFREY TORRES BELLO

Electronic Engineer

// E

EDUCATION & COURSES

PLATZI

Fundamentos Js.

Curso de React.js & React Avanzado Curso profesional de Git y Github

ED TEAM

CSS, html, Pug.

UDEMY

Flutter basic with Fernando Herrera Flutter advanced Dr. Angela Yu Vscode Fernando Herrera

20 September 2020 Barranquila, Colombia COURSERA | UNIVERSITY OF ALBERTA

Design Patterns

2014 - 2018 UNIVERSIDAD DEL NORTE
Barranquila, Colombia Degree of electronic engineering

2003 - 2013 Valledupar, Colombia SAGRADA FAMILIA

High school

EXPERIENCE

TECHNISUPPORT S.A.S

March 2018 - Present

react-native developer, state management with redux middlewares like redux-saga, redux-thunk, redux-persist, push notifications(firebase), and testing with Jest

WORKLY

November 2018 - Present

ReactJs(Hooks) developer, deployment using GitHub actions and firebase hosting, routing with react-router, styling Sass.

UNIVERSIDAD DEL NORTE - DEGREE THESIS

June 2018 - November 2019

ReactJs developer,redux, firebase, maps

GOCARGO S.A.S

Noviembre 2018 - Marzo 2019

React-native, Android, IOS, GIT, Redux, Redux sagas, Redux Thunk. Push notifications, Firebase. App store Connect, Play Console



PROJECTS

WorklyApp Fullstack

Mobile application using react-native, implementing redux, axios, push notifications, back end using expressJs, Mongodb, socket.io, Json web token hosted in Heroku.

Dificultad preoperatorio Colelap

Flutter development.



REFERENCES

Eily Mejia

UI/UX Lead in Lean Tech IO Phone: 3016832030 Fabian Diartt Electronic engineer Phone: 3045929332